Welcome back to the webcast where we spotlight some of the crew's people and projects in the ecosystem and today we joined by Ben, CMO of Radium.
I remember going to my first breakpoint in 2022 and the FTX collapse was happening and I looked around the room and I said, these guys are never leaving Suana.
Three years ago BlackRock was like, no, no, we hate crypto.
It's funny how quickly the world changed.
So we went through this evolution of being this infrastructure provider in the background to being a full stack liquidity provider and full stack trading tool.
And a big part of that obviously was expansion to perpetuals, which is where the partnership reportedly came in.
I think curbs will always be interesting.
I think generally people care less about owning the asset and they want to care about having exposure to the asset.
I've been in this industry for five years and these are the rooms that us crypto people were shunned in and now suddenly we got the suits in the room.
I think we are still in this speculative era of crypto where primarily people look at it as a way to make money and just better financial management.
But I think we're starting to inch towards more of the utility phase of crypto.